Welcome to the second day of the Summer
Tournament West Kyushu Qualifiers!
Shitou Suisan 2nd Year
Ganeko Mayu
Kairyou Academy 2nd Year
Inui Saki
The thirty-first match has just ended!
Kairyou Academy 2nd Year
Inui Saki
The star of mighty Shitou Suisan, Ganeko Mayu,
Milady!
was just defeated by Kairyou Academy's
Inui, in her first tournament appearance!
That means the final will feature this
tournament's fastest speeder, Inui,
Kairyou Academy 2nd Year
Inui Saki
Takafuji Academy 3rd Year
Shindou Kazunari
taking on the King of Kings, Shindou!
Will Inui's speed prove
effective against Shindou?
Really, Asuka-senpai was so amazing!
For a moment, I actually
thought she might win!
Yeah...
You were so close, too, Misaki-senpai!
The two of you were seriously awesome!
Yeah, I guess.
I did my best.
I put up a great fight against Shindou-san.
Episode Seven:
"Sting Before You're Stung!"
Good day, madam.
It's a honor to meet you.
My name is Irina Avalon.
You're from Kairyou, right?
Yes.
Second of Inui Saki.
So you're the one who coached her?
Yes.
Saki and I started FC after being
inspired by Kagami Aoi.
Please watch the next match.
We will have something interesting in store.
That match was incredible!
I'd never seen anyone do consecutive
air kick turns before!
How do you time them?
How do you normally train?
Are you really a beginner?
Er...
Wow, she's suddenly the center of attention.
But of course. She did make Captain Shindou
get serious, if only for a moment.
I know, right?
Why are you puffing your chest out?
Hard luck, Misaki.
The manner in which you took
it to a dogfight was great.
One more push might've changed everything.
He's right, isn't he?
Yeah.
The final will begin shortly.
On your marks...
Set!
The final match has just begun!
A conventional start, with Inui
making a beeline for the buoy
and Shindou taking a shortcut
to the second line.
Inui-san really is crazy quick.
There's no telling how this match will go.
Well, I think it's gonna
be a one-sided contest.
Really?
I mean, Inui's speed is the only
thing she's got going for her.
Shindou-san should be able
to brush her off with ease.
Point to Inui! 0-1!
Inui grabs the initiative
with the first point.
Now, how will the defending champion respond?
Talk about fast, yeesh.
She got me with that sudden elevation, too.
Point to Shindou!
That didn't take long. Shindou
has already evened the score.
Point to Shindou! 2-1!
That's the King for you.
He's showing off his royal spirit and muscles.
He took the lead from behind!
Way to go, Captain!
Show them that Takafuji isn't
called a powerhouse for nothing!
Oh man, they're way up in the sky!
The two of them have chased each other
to quite an unbelievable altitude!
Whoa, they're more than 200 meters high now.
Are they gonna race into space?
Quit spacing out.
Now, Saki.
Okay, Irina.
Inui's going after the third buoy,
but Shindou keeps blocking her path.
Can she get past him and take the buoy,
or will Shindou turn this into a dogfight?
Right now, Shindou-san's
in the driver's seat.
Yeah. He's heading her off every time.
Amazing.
Right? Nothing less from Shindou-san.
You're wrong.
What do you mean?
Inui-san's the one who's amazing.
No way. He's in the lead.
And he keeps cutting her off before
she can get to the third buoy.
That's just because she's forcing him to.
What the hell?
Kurashina's right.
Although Shindou-san may be heading her off,
Inui's countering that with a
steady and deliberate descent.
If he continues trying to block her path...
...he'll eventually be
forced down to the surface.
And if that happens, he'll
be at a clear disadvantage.
M-Maybe it's just a coincidence?
It could've just turned out that way
while he was chasing her around.
Knowing Shindou-san, that's impossible.
L-Look at him...
It can't be.
C-Captain?!
Shindou seemed to have Inui under control,
but he gave up the fight and
moved on to the next line!
He bailed?
Point to Inui! 2-2!
Now the score is tied!
Oh, are they having another race to the top?
Not this again!
Saki...
Okay, Irina.
It's the second line all over again.
He's being steered downwards.
This doesn't look good.
He's being utterly controlled.
Controlled?
Inui never planned on taking
the buoys or dogfighting.
The only thing on her mind was to
control and dominate her opponent!
"Dominate"? What's that even supposed to mean?
Isn't Flying Circus all about touching
the buoys or your opponent's back?
Captain! At this rate, you'll be
helpless to fend off another point!
A vertical air kick turn to turn the tide!
Now he can get above...
If FC were to be dominated by tactics counter to the spirit of the game,
its evolution would crash headlong into a brick wall
and it would meet its demise as a major sport.
That's why I decided to seal
away that tactic forevermore.
He's using the recoil to take the buoy!
He's got this!
End it, Saki.
Okay, Irina.
This match is over!
Inui wins!
In what can only be called
a bizarre end to the final,
Inui Saki emerges victorious!
She has taken out reigning champion
Shindou in an upset for the ages!
No way, Shindou-san...
Incredible!
Asuka?
Wasn't that simply incredible?
So this is Flying Circus, too.
How can she be beaming like
that after what we saw?
I...
I just don't understand.
All-Japan Flying Circus Summer Tournament West Kyushu Qualifiers
Ganeko Mayu
Inui Saki
Shindou Kazunari
Where's Misaki?
She left. Said she was beat.
Jeez. She really does march
to the beat of her own drum.
All-Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
"Birdcage."
That is the name we came up
with for our beautiful FC move.
Your play style? "Beautiful"?
A tactic to dominate opponents completely.
The beautiful brand of FC you created.
Let us meet again.
Good-bye.
Guess I have yet to fully atone for
the sin of dabbling in the forbidden.
Misaki...
Are ya done with your homework?
Nah, not yet.
I'm glad you're helpin' out,
but summer break's endin' soon.
You gotta get ready to go back to school.
Got it.
By the way, didn't you have some
school-related plans for today?
Nah. I've got nothing.
That so.
All right, then.
I'm Kurashina Asuka! Here I go!
Good.
Nice spirit there, Kurashina.
I'm gonna jump, too!
It's all about spirit!
J-Jellyfish!
There's a jellyfish by my feet!
It's really slimy!
Help! I'm scared!
All you need to deal with
jellyfish venom is spirit.
In fact...
Sting before you're stung.
Make sure you don't get hurt, you two!
Sheesh...
I wish Misaki-senpai had come.
I would've been able to
see her in a swimsuit.
Mashiro!
Misaki-senpai!
What can ya do? She said
something suddenly came up.
The meat should be ready soon.
Yeah.
Oh, Madoka. Could you get everyone?
Sure!
I'm waiting for meat!
Well, wait just a bit longer.
The meat is great too,
but so's the shrimp and squid.
We owe Satouin-san big time.
Yeah.
Since she couldn't make it,
she had the Satou Group send
us the best seafood possible.
"Satou Group"...?
Always the enigma, that Satouin-san.
Thank you for coming too, Shirase-san.
You even brought us meat.
You guys put up a great fight
in the summer tournament.
This is the least we could
do to show our appreciation.
Besides...
We were told today was an important day.
"Important...
...day"?
That's right!
Today, I want to inform
you of a major decision
concerning Kunahama High's FC team.
I'm a lucky, lucky man.
After spending so long alone,
I got to participate in the
tournament with you guys,
and even had a decent showing.
However, my dream of victory in the
regionals has yet to be fulfilled!
So I want you guys to make it come true.
Understood!
I want to make the captain's dream come true!
Knowing you, Asuka-senpai,
you could actually win!
After how well you guys did
in the summer tournament,
it might not be a mere pipe dream.
I agree.
In that case, please stay on as coach
until the end of the fall tournament.
O-Okay...
All right! Let's all win together!
Sure.
Guys...
Although practice might get tough
as the fall tournament draws closer,
always have fun flying.
Please don't forget that.
Got it!
Shall we have Kurashina
succeed me as captain, then?
Sir, I have a question!
Okay, shoot.
What does a captain do?
Anybody else?
You leave me no choice!
I graciously volunteer
to be the next captain.
I'm taking over as main heroine!
All in favor of Madoka taking
over as captain, say, "Aye."
Aye...
H-Hey! Aren't you guys being
a bit too blasé about this?
Aren't these things supposed
to be done with more fanfare?
Please get me some meat, new Captain.
Me too, please.
Apathetic! Way too apathetic!
Hurry up with the meat!
Oh, here you go—
Wait, no!
I'm sad we couldn't hang out today. (>_<)
Let's do our best in the fall tournament!
What? Misaki-senpai went out?
Oh, you hadn't heard?
She said this morning that she
was going to Fukuru Island.
Oh...
And here I came to give her
a surprise udon delivery.
Darn it.
Whoa, it's Shito-kun!
He's so scary!
I'm not scared at all.
Come on, don't cry.
There!
No!
Stop crying, c'mon!
Stop it, bro!
Thank you very much!
What am I doing?
I had one of these already.
Why'd I get soba?
What am I doing?
It's time for this week's Shito Channel news!
This year's Flying Circus Regional
Qualifiers caused quite the stir
as the defending champion was defeated
by a player making her first appearance.
She carried that momentum into the All-Japans as well, emerging victorious
and attracting widespread attention!
Did you hear about that?
Apparently Shindou-senpai lost to a newcomer.
For real? I don't believe it!
I heard that she goes to Kairyou Academy.
I didn't know Kairyou had such a wunderkind.
Ugh, it's raining.
I can't fly home now.
Guess I'll just take the ferry.
Archipelago Bus Transport
Iron Mall
This isn't gonna let up anytime soon.
It's you.
First time since the summer tourney, huh?
Yes.
Here shopping?
Yeah, since summer break's ending and all.
Summer break?
Oh, right. It's summer break right now.
Did you come here to shop too?
Yeah, to buy running gear
and some supplements.
Running gear?
Don't tell me you're switching
to track and field.
No way.
It's for FC, of course.
For FC?
College players are way ahead
of us in terms of physique.
So I figured I should build up
my body by the time I graduate.
How?
How can you be that positive?
After how you lost...
I'm sorry! That was rude of me!
Nah, it's okay.
That match did come as a shock to me, too.
I got scared, as it felt like everything
I'd done had been dismissed out of hand.
If you got scared, then why?
Because the fear of losing something
shows that you enjoy it.
That match made me realize
that FC is a sport in which
a play style that was effective up to
last year could stop working at any moment—
a sport in which everything can change overnight.
And being able to experience that
first-hand is awesome, don't you think?
Change can be scary.
But if you can overcome that,
you can have a whole lot of fun.
Is that really fun?
If I ever stop finding it fun,
I'll quit.
Right...
Aren't you getting on?
Oh, I just remembered
something else I had to buy.
I'll take the next bus.
Oh, okay. Later.
It's finally the start of a new term!
Time for practice!
You seem full of spirit, Asuka.
I am!
I want to fly so badly, I
can hardly control myself!
Good morning!
Wait, what?
Isn't Misaki-senpai here yet?
Wasn't she with you?
Her grandmother told me she left early today,
so I thought she'd be here already.
What's wrong, Madoka?
Never mind me! This is awful!
Jeez, what is it?
What's got you so agitated?
Notice of Withdrawal
Flying Circus Team
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Wha—
N-No way...
What?
W-Wait, what?
Y-Y-You're kidding, right?
What do we do?
Misaki-chan...
To Be Continued
Preview
Asuka!
Misaki-chan...
Misaki-senpai!
I... can't fly anymore.
Episode Eight:
"I... Can't Fly Anymore."